export const MathHard = [
  {
    question: "Name a triangle whose two angles are equal.",
    Options: ["Right angle triangle.", "Isosceles triangle.", "Scalene triangle.", "None of these."],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many lines can be drawn through two points?",
    Options: ["1", "2", "3", "Not possible."], 
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Factors of 9 are.....",
    Options: ["1, 2 and 3", "1, 2, 3 and 9", "1, 6 and 9", "None of these."],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "When we multiply an exact number by zero what will be the exact answer?",
    Options: ["the exact number.", "cannot be multiplied.", "zero .", "None of these."],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits answer we will get when we add 99 and 1?",
    Options: ["1", "3", "99", "100"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many cents is equal to $1?",
    Options: ["15", "20", "25", "30"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many months are equal to 45 days?",
    Options: ["1 1/2 months", "114 months", "14 months", "2 1/4 months"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many diagonals are there in a quadrilateral?",
    Options: ["2", "3", "4", "N diagonals"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Speed of a car is 60 km/hr. Distance covered in 1 1/4 hours is",
    Options: ["60 km", "65 km", "70 km", "75 km"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "If one side of a square is 35 m, then the area is",
    Options: ["1252 m²", "1225 m²", "1252 m", "1225 m"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many surfaces are there in a cube?",
    Options: ["3", "4", "5", "None of these"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How much water is added to 750 g milk to get 1 kilogram mixture of liquid?",
    Options: ["5 kg", "0.25 kg", "20.5 kg", "25.0 kg"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "An acute angle is",
    Options: ["90 degree", "less than 90 degree", "more than 90 degree", "None of these"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many parts are there in a triangle?",
    Options: ["3", "6 times", "9", "None of these"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which unit is used to measure length and breadth?",
    Options: ["Scale", "Meter", "Liter", "Gram"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is 999 times 100.0?",
    Options: ["199.0", "999.0", "9990", "99900"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the unit of volume?",
    Options: ["square units", "cubic units", "only unit", "None of these"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "1010 gram = kg.",
    Options: ["10 kg", "101.0 kg", "001 kg", "01 kg"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How many times 1000 is bigger than 1?",
    Options: ["1 time", "10 times", "100 times", "1000 times"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Average of three person's age is 9 years. Find the sum of their age.",
    Options: ["18", "21", "24", "27"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  }
];
